Prentiss Taylor
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1885-1991, undated, Series 10:; (Box 3-21, OV 22; 18.0 linear feet; Reels 5913-5935)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1939-1956 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 104-105)
  - Pierre Daura, 1976 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 107)
  - Carson Davenport, 1939-1967, (4 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 109-225)
  - Davidson Galleries, 1990 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 227-231)
  - Gene Davis, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 233-235)
  - Gwen Davis, 1981 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 237-238)
  - James G. Davis, 1983 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 246-257)
  - Marni Ayres Davis, 1924-1928 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 259-297)
  - R. E. Davis & Son, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 299-304)
  - Agnes and William Dawson, 1956-1963 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 306-310)
  - Carley Dawson, undated (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 312-313)
  - Charles B. Dawson, 1956 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 315-316)
  - Mary Doolittle Dawson, 1954-1962 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 318-320)
  - Jane Deal, 1966 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 322-323)
  - Russ and Jo Dean, undated (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 325-326)
  - De Cordova Museum, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 328-330)
  - Adolf Dehn, undated (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 332-333)
  - Agnes Delano and Marion Delano Fuller, 1947-1963 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 335-365)
  - Josephine M. Delin, 1928-1956 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 367-391)
  - Nevin M. Dellinger, 1958 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 393)
  - Delores Del Rio, 1983 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 395)
  - Marguerite De M., 1975 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 397)
  - Inez Demonet, 1943-1975 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 399-415)
  - Ludwell Denny, 1970 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 417)
  - M. Robert Deo, 1957 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 419-420)
  - John De Pol, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 422-424)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1949 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 426)
  - Mrs. Jacob Detwiler, 1958 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 428)
  - Dorothy Detzer, 1981 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 430)
  - Charles R. Dick, 1979 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 432)
  - Edward F. Dickerson and Wendell E. Dickerson, 1957 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 434-444)
  - Margaret P. Dickey Gallery of Art, 1958-1963 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 446-448)
  - Emily Dickinson, undated (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 450)
  - Preston Dickinson, 1928-1979 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 452-500)
  - Constance Dietschy, 1961-1973 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 502-508)
  - Margaret Disney, 1963 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 510-511)
  - District of Columbia Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1981 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 513)
  - District of Columbia Institute of Mental Hygiene, 1975 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 515-516)
  - District of Columbia Mental Health Association, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 518-527)
  - Sharon Pratt Dixon, 1990 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 529-535)
  - Alice Dodge, 1955 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 537-538)
  - Lilian T. Dodge, 1958 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 540-541)
  - C. L. Dodgson (Lewis Carroll?), 1895 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 543-544)
  - Owen Dodson, 1954-1983 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 546-551)
  - Dolan Maxwell Gallery, 1984 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 553-554)
  - Elizabeth Dominick, 1947-1954 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 556-569)
  - George A. Dondero, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 571-599)
  - Tom Donnelly, 1976 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 601-602)
  - Otto Donner, 1981 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 604)
  - Anne Dougherty, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 606-618)
  - Bertha Dougherty, 1951 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 620-621)
  - Laura Douglas, 1950-1962 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 623-631)
  - Lester Douglas, 1949 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 633-645)
  - Paul Douglas, 1976 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 647-649)
  - Sharon E. Dove, 1980 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 651)
  - Dover, New Hampahire, 1954 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 653-654)
  - Betty Dow, 1941 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 656-657)
  - Kenneth Dow, 1942-1952 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 659-671)
  - Carmen and Olin Dows, 1979 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 673-676)
  - Miss Dreier, 1950 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 678)
  - Esther Dreifus, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 680-691)
  - Lulu Drennan, 1960 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 693)
  - Werner Drewes, 1928-1987 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 695-733)
  - Jean Dubuffet, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 735-740)
  - Robert E. Duffy, 1983 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 742-750)
  - Angier Biddle Duke, undated (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 752)
  - Nancy Dunaway, 1957 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 754-755)
  - Ralph A. Dungan, 1961 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 757-758)
  - Katharine Dunlap, 1938-1970 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 760-770)
  - Charles Dunn, 1959-1978 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 772-780)
  - Dupont Laundry, 1978 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 782)
  - Dupont Theatre Art Gallery, 1949-1954 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 784-787)
  - Laura Dupuy, 1960 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 789-790)
  - John and Betsy Dutton, 1952-1980 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 792-808)
  - W. E., 1937-1939 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 811-814)
  - Kathryn T. Eager, 1963 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 816-819)
  - Thomas Eakins, undated (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 821-824)
  - Easter Islands, undated (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 826-827)
  - John C. Eastlack, 1888 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 829)
  - Julia Eckel, 1936 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 831-836)
  - Nancy Edelman, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 838-845)
  - Bob Edwards, 1939 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 847-848)
  - Cliff Edwards, 1971 (Box 8, Reel 5919)
  - David Edwards, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 851-868)
  - Eddie Edwards, 1949 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 870)
  - Dorothy S. Egbert, 1951 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 872-873)
  - Lyn Egbert, 1955-1977 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 875-888)
  - Nancy L. Egbert, 1952 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 890-891)
  - James Wytche Elder, 1961-1981 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 893-895)
  - Deborah Ellis (Mrs. Llewellyn B. Bigelow), 1966-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 897-920)
  - Helen Elser, 1961 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 922)
  - Emerson Gallery, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 924-945)
  - Louise Emerson, 1951-1975 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 947-954)
  - John English, 1931-1932, (Includes oversized materials from Box 21) (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 956-980)
  - Peggy Erckmann, 1964 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 982-983)
  - Elizabeth N. Erlanger, 1966-1973 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 985-989)
  - Dr. Erskine, 1951 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 991)
  - Katherine "Katy" Gibbs Ericsson and Samuel Ericsson, 1941-1977 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 993-1028)
  - Dick Eskilson?, 1961 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1030-1031)
  - Richard Ettinghausen, 1979 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1033)
  - Lyle Evan Gallery, 1983 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1035)
  - Edith Evans, 1976 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1037)
  - Emily A. Evans, 193-1954 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1039-1042)
  - Frank Evans, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1044-1078)
  - Lucile Evans, 1953-1962 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1080-1086)
  - Maurice Evans, 1935 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1088-1089)
  - Stephanie Evans, 1979 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1091-1092)
  - Robert Evett, 1975 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1094-1095)
  - Max Ewing, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1097-1107)
  - Emily L. Faber, 1960 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1109)
  - Ralph Fabri, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1111-1116)
  - Sergio Fabris, 1954 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1118)
  - Donald Stites Fairchild, 1933-1939 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1120-1138)
  - Fairfax County Cultural Association, Inc., 1970 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1140-1141)
  - Fairfax Unitarian Church, 1964 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1143)
  - Dorothy Fall, 1984 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1145-1146)
  - Leslie Farber, 1981 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1148)
  - Phyllis R. Faria, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1150-1157)
  - Farnsworth Art Museum and Library, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1159-1167)
  - Farrar & Rinehart, Publishers, 1940 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1169)
  - Henry Lawrence Faulkner, 1953-1958 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1171-1182)
  - William Faulkner, 1962 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1185)
  - Federal Resrve Bank Slide Registry, undated (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1187)
  - Herbert and Ruth Feis, 1956-1965 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1189-1221)
  - Aline Feldman, 1967-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1223-1228)
  - Fendrick Gallery, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1230-1231)
  - Alan Fern, 1982 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1233)
  - Leslie Fernandez, 1969-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1235-1237)
  - Byrd Ferneyhough, 1966 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1239-1240)
  - Clare Ferriter, 1963-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1242-1247)
  - Frances Ferry, 1949-1966 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1249-1270)
  - Herb Fichter, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1272-1274)
  - Rachel Field, 1927-1951, (3 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1276-1403)
  - Ruth Filip, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1405-1407)
  - Irving Fineman, 1932-1936 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1409-1412)
  - John F. Finerty, 1967 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1423)
  - First Virginia Bank, 1982 (Box 8, Reel 5919, Frame 1425-1429)
  - Davira Fisher, 1960-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 13-39)
  - M. T. Fisher, 1964 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 41)
  - Richard Arnold Fisher, 1926 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 43-48)
  - Bradley Fisk, 1962 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 50)
  - Fisk University, 1933-1955 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 52-60)
  - Fitchburg Art Museum, 1980 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 62-65)
  - Bill Fitts, 1960-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 67-77)
  - Fitz, 1935 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 79)
  - Mrs. Fitzpatrick, 1947 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 81)
  - Muriel Fitzpatrick, 1966 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 83)
  - Bunny Flanagan, 1961 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 85-86)
  - John Flannagan, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 88-90)
  - Janet Flint, 1975-1984 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 92-95)
  - Peggy and Richard Flint, 1941-1972 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 97-119)
  - Frances Foote, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 121-122)
  - James Forbes, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 124-129)
  - John R. Forbes, 1946 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 131-134)
  - Ford Foundation, 1958 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 136-148)
  - Foreign Service Journal, 1958 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 150)
  - Barbara Forman, 1953 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 152-153)
  - James Forsythe, 1982 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 155)
  - Fort Meade, Maryland, 1946 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 157)
  - William F. Foshag, 1956 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 159)
  - Genevieve and Roger Foster, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 161-162)
  - Alfred Fowler, 1948-1952 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 164-170)
  - Emily Francis, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 172)
  - Sandra P. Francklin, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 174-177)
  - Adele and Vincent Franks, 1942-1960 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 179-233)
  - Frederick William Frear, 1936-1968 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 235-250)
  - Mrs. Max Freedman, 1967 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 252)
  - Don Freeman, 1978 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 254)
  - John French, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 256-257)
  - Ray H. French (Depauw University), 1959-1963 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 259-270)
  - F. A. Freyhan, 1951 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 272-273)
  - Amos Fries, 1933 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 275-293)
  - Frances Frost, 1932 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 295-318)
  - Jack Fullilove, 1942-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 320-356)
  - Donald G., 1974-1980 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 358-359)
  - Lucy G., 1973 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 361)
  - V. V. G., 1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 363-364)
  - Bob and Ardis Gabel, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 366-368)
  - Dr. Gallagher, 1985 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 370)
  - G. C. Gallagher, 1984 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 372-373)
  - Mary C. Gallagher, 1963 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 375-376)
  - Gallery 4, Alexandria, Virginia, 1978 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 378-381)
  - Gallery 10, Washington, D. C., 1980 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 383-384)
  - Gallery 313, Washington, D. C., 1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 386-389)
  - Don Gallup, 1959-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 391-396)
  - Ruth Galloon, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 398-408)
  - Hester and Robert Galvin, 1970 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 410-411)
  - Lewis and Ruth Gannett, 1966-1979 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 413-419)
  - Helen Gardner, 1954-1969 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 421-424)
  - Beryl Garrott, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 426)
  - Saul I. Gass, 1961 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 428)
  - Margaret Casey Gates and Robert F. Gates, 1934-1982 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 430-447)
  - Paul Gaunt, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 449-488)
  - Thomas N. Gee, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 490-501)
  - Henry Geldzahler, 1977 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 503)
  - Ellen Gelman, 1962-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 505-511)
  - Arnold Genthe, 1936 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 513-515)
  - Phyllis Bowles Georg, 1956 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 517)
  - Louise George, 1964 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 519-521)
  - Georgetown University, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 523-526)
  - George Washington University, 1965-1973 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 528-537)
  - James Geralis, 1956 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 539-541)
  - Helen Gerardia, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 543-563)
  - Doreen Gerlach, 1958 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 565-567)
  - Margaret N. Germond, 1966 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 569)
  - John Gernand, 1936-1983 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 571-635)
  - John Gerrard, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 637-654)
  - Eugenie Gershoy, 1950 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 656-657)
  - Elsa and Herbert Gerst, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 659-660)
  - Libby Getz, 1967-1979 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 662-672)
  - Al and Margot Gianascol, 1954 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 674-704)
  - Elio Gianturco, 1953 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 706)
  - Gibbes Art Gallery (see also Carolina Art Associaton), 1933-1985 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 708-770)
  - Margaret Gibson, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 772)
  - V. C. Gibson, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 774-775)
  - Marie Gilchrist, 1928-1937 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 777-809)
  - Mrs. Donald Giles, 1955 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 811)
  - Duff Gilfond, 1946 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 813)
  - Alberto Ginastera, 1983 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 815)
  - Elizabeth Ginnis?, 1956 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 817-818)
  - Alberto Gironella, 1959 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 820-825)
  - C. Leslie Glenn, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 827-835)
  - Gloucester School of the Little Theatre, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 837-852)
  - Frederick R. Goff, 1982 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 854)
  - Eva Goldbeck, 1928 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 856-857)
  - Lucien Goldschmidt, 1956-1971 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 859-871)
  - Ben and Beatrice Goldstein Foundation, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 873-879)
  - Anne and Lucy Goldthwaite, 1933-1983 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 881-917)
  - Lucy Gomersall, 1956-1971 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 919-923)
  - Elena Gonzalez, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 925)
  - Walter Scott Goodine, 1963 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 927)
  - Caroline L. Gordon, 1933-1958, (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 929-1050)
  - Grace Gorlitz, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1052-1056)
  - Jac Gorodetzky, 1955 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1058)
  - Edith Gove, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1060-1068)
  - Ralph Gove, 1954 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1070-1073)
  - Mrs. Percy P. Grady, 1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1075)
  - Liliana Gramberg, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1077-1086)
  - Donald Gramm, 1983 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1088)
  - Graphic Arts Council of New York, 1981 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1090-1097)
  - Ann and Wolf Graubard, 1959 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1099-1101)
  - Lillian Graves, 1933-1946 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1103-1117)
  - Mortimer Graves, 1955 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1119)
  - Graylyn, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1121-1142)
  - Greater Washington Invitational Art Show, 1972 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1144-1145)
  - Frances Green, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1147-1158)
  - Gretchen Green, undated (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1160-1163)
  - Henri and Jim Green, 1951-1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1165-1168)
  - Theodore F. Green, 1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1170)
  - Dorothea S. Greenbaum, 1939-1976 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1172-1262)
  - Marvin Grieve, 1947 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1264-1266)
  - Tatyana Grossman, 1976 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1268)
  - Bob Grove, 1991 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1270)
  - Jean and Edward R. Grove, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1272-1280)
  - Martha Gruering, 1933-1937 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1282-1313)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1933-1939 (Box 8, Reel 5920, Frame 1315-1350)
  - Loring H., 1946-1953 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1353-1384)
  - Margaret Hagan, 1966 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1386)
  - Frank Gardner Hale, 1933 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1388-1389)
  - Alfredo Halegua, undated (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1391)
  - Delight Hall, 1964 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1393)
  - Peggy Scott Hall, 1964 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1395-1396)
  - Corrie Halsey, 1973 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1398-1399)
  - George H. Hamilton, 1935-1956 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1401-1428)
  - Genevieve Hamper, 1971 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1430)
  - Hanford Press, 1952 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1432)
  - Roger Hansel, 1975 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1434)
  - Frances Leich Hanson (Mrs. Richard L. Hanson), 1951-1979 (Box 9, Reel 5920, Frame 1436-1501)
  - Janice Harrington, 1946 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 13-14)
  - Beverly H. Harris, 1959 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 16)
  - Dorothy Harrison, 1957-1971 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 18-40)
  - Wallace Harrison, 1981 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 42)
  - Horace Hart, 1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 44-48)
  - Muriel Hart, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 50)
  - Amora C. Harvey, 1983 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 52)
  - Victor Hasenoehrl, 1986 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 54)
  - Nagel Haskin, 1973 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 56)
  - Jane Haslem, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 58-75)
  - Hotel Hassler, Rome, 1966 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 77)
  - Hatfield's Color Shop, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 79-80)
  - James D. Havens, 1956-1959 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 82-93)
  - Erik Hawkins, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 95-96)
  - Charles W. Hawthorne, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 98-100)
  - Edith Haydon, 1967 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 102)
  - William Hays, 1978 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 104)
  - E.? Heard, 1960 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 106-107)
  - Paul Heard, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 109-110)
  - Henriette Hooper Heath, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 112-114)
  - Inga Wall Heck, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 116)
  - Victor R. Heflin, 1974 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 118)
  - Laurence and Marilyn Heilprin, 1957 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 120-123)
  - Arthur Heintzelman, 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 125)
  - Janet and Naida Henderson, 1980 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 127-128)
  - Jack W. Henry, 1964-1982 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 130-131)
  - Clara Herbert, 1957 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 133)
  - Henry Herman, 1938 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 135-139)
  - John A. Herring, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 141-161)
  - Nancy Hersch, 1973 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 163-167)
  - Pierre Herson, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 169-170)
  - Helene and Philip Herzbrun, 1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 172-173)
  - Lin and Wilmer Clyde Hewitt, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 175-178)
  - Dorothy Heyward, 1944-1961 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 180-190)
  - Granville Hicks, 1982 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 192)
  - Martin Hiden, 1948-1952 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 194-204)
  - Eugene Higgins, 1946 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 206)
  - Jean and Marion Hildebrand, 1950-1987 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 208-214)
  - Helen Hill, 1981 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 216-217)
  - Laura Hill, 1941-1953 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 219-220)
  - Winifred Hill, 1940 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 222-232)
  - Hill-Lederer Gallery, 1960 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 235-236)
  - John Hillery, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 238-251)
  - Ernest Hillman, 1948-1952 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 253-257)
  - Allonell Hines, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 259-260)
  - Marjorie Hirano, 1967-1980 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 262-281)
  - Un-Ichi Hiratsuka, 1966-1979 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 283-308)
  - Joseph Hirsch, 1981 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 310-311)
  - Joe Hirschman, 1944-1954 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 313-359)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, Smithsonian Institution, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 361-366)
  - Angelo Hodick, 1974 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 368-377)
  - Polly Parker Hoff, 1956-1960 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 379-382)
  - Phyllis Hoffman, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 384-393)
  - Hofstra University, 1985 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 395-397)
  - Inez Hogan, 1926 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 399-403)
  - Beth Holderbachs, 1978 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 405-407)
  - Libby Holman, 1983 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 409)
  - Mary Hone, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 411-422)
  - Richard E. Hood, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 424-427)
  - Henry T. Hooper, 1959 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 429-433)
  - Allan Hoover, Jr., 1964 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 435-436)
  - Hoover Company, 1978 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 438)
  - DeWolf Hopper, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 440)
  - Francis H. Horan, 1952-1962 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 442-448)
  - Grace Horne Galleries, 1938-1944 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 450-460)
  - Mardi Horowitz, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 462-467)
  - Norman Horowitz, 1954 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 469)
  - Herbert Hosmer, 1941-1954 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 471-489)
  - James Freeman Hottel and Ruby Perry Hottel, 1910-1962 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 491-585)
  - James Freeman Hottel and Ruby Perry Hottel, 1910-1962 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 587-588)
  - Katharine A. Hottel, 1935-1981, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 590-599)
  - Lucy and Martin Perry Hottel, 1961-1981 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 601-619)
  - House of Mercy, 1957 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 621-628)
  - Howard University, 1950-1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 630-646)
  - Walter Bruce Howe, Mary Howe, and Bruce Howe, 1941-1975 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 648-695)
  - Richard Howland, 1956 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 697-699)
  - Gizella Huber, 1963 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 701-702)
  - Andrew Hudson, 1978 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 704-705)
  - Langston Hughes, 1931-1982, (41 folders; includes oversized materials from Box 21) (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 707-1310)
  - Ruth Fox Hume, 1980 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1312)
  - Peter Hunt, 1967 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1314)
  - Hunterdon Art Center, 1967-1974 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1316-1348)
  - Victoria Hutson Huntley, 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1350)
  - Mary Huntoon, 1953-1959 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1352-1355)
  - Zora Neale Hurston, 1985, undated, (5 folders) (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1357-1365)
  - Janet Hurter, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1367-1380)
  - Josephine Hutchinson, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1382-1383)
  - Birdie Hutton, 1953 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1385-1386)
  - Alfred Hutty, undated (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1388-1389)
  - Hygeia, 1924 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1391)
  - I.B.M. Gallery, 1968 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1393-1394)
  - I.F.A. Galleries, 1951 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1396)
  - Department of the Interior, 1961-1985 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1398-1405)
  - Carlotta Irwin, 1927 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1407-1408)
  - Elizabeth Irwin, 1931-1936 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1410-1420)
  - Leila Irwin, 1963-1977 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1422-1427)
  - William Irwin, 1928 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1429-1430)
  - Harold B. Isen, 1967-1974 (Box 9, Reel 5921, Frame 1441-1446)
  - Sheila Isham (Mrs. Heyward Isham), 1960-1979, (2 folders) (Box 9, Reel 5922, Frame 13-79)
  - Michio Ito, 1961 (Box 9, Reel 5922, Frame 81)
  - Anne Ives, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Reel 5922, Frame 83-87)
  - Paul J., 1930-1931 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 90-98)
  - Billy Morrow Jackson, 1956-1964, (3 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 100-185)